jobtome.com 2018-07-23

# Jobtome.com | One site. All jobs.

## 1\. References about Data Controller

Jobtome International SA (owner of the brand and of the website “Jobtome” / “Jobtome.com”) handles all personal data of users and guests in full accordance with the provisions of the European privacy legislation.

## 2\. Data collected through browsing

We collect information about you to provide our services. In order for us to best provide our services to you (and to help make it feasible for us to do so), it is essential that we are able to collect and use the information as described in this Policy. When you visit Jobtome, we gather some personal data, such as pages viewed, links or buttons clicked, date and time of access, your IP address, the browser used and your operating system (following “Browsing Data”), that will be used only to obtain anonymous statistical information on the use of the website or for purposes strictly linked to its running. Furthermore, we track the opening of emails that notify new jobs and the number of clicks on attached links for statistical purposes.

## 3\. Data voluntarily provided

Your email address: Jobtome allows you to create a system for the notification of new job offers (Job Alert). The activation of the notification occurs through the input of the User's email address, name, surname, the geographical area and/or the professional field in which you would like to monitor ads. The effective enrollment at the Job alert service is subject to the current privacy policy and to service conditions. The email address can be entered manually, through the identification service of Facebook, provided by Facebook Inc or through the one-tap sign-up feature provided by Google. Through authentication, Facebook or Google provide access to some basic information of your profile and other information related to permissions you give when you authorize our application. Aside from the notification of new notices, Jobtome may send you specific job offers. These offers come from our partners who are interested in the professional figures you are tracking. Jobtome reserves the right to send to your e-mail address also commercial communications or advertising of services of its property or coming from third parties, including also external companies employed by Jobtome. As soon as you cancel the reception of the Job Alert, the service will be interrupted. Interruption and removal can also occur under other conditions, for example in the event that you stop clicking the link attached in your emails for a long period of time.

## 4\. Manner and place of retention of personal data

We handle your data according to the law, taking all appropriate security measures aimed to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or unauthorized destruction of Personal Data. The retention is done with tools, both manual and computerized and / or telematic, with organizational procedures and with logic strictly related to the stated purposes. Personal Data are handled at the registered office of the Data Controller and, according to services provided by third parties, also the ones outside the Country and/or outside the European Union the data are kept for the time necessary to perform the service you have requested, and deleted at the fading of the purposes for which they were collected and treated.

## 6\. Privacy of Minors

To access or use the Platform you must be 13 years of age or older and, if under 18 or the age of majority in your jurisdiction, your use of Platform must be under the supervision of a parent or guardian or other responsible adult. If you become aware that a child has provided us with personal information without parental consent, please contact us [here](https://us.jobtome.com/contact-us). If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information without parental consent, we remove such information and terminate the child's account.

## 7\. Data controller

The information about you that we collect, process and/or use through the Platform is controlled by Jobtome International SA, Switerland. You may reach our data protection officer [here](https://us.jobtome.com/contact-us)

## 8\. Users Rights

You have the right to [contact Jobtome](https://us.jobtome.com/contact-us), at the given contact addresses, to obtain:

  * the confirmation of the existence of your Personal Data and, if so, the list of Personal Data in possession of Jobtome;

  * information on the terms and purposes of the processing of your Personal Information;

  * updating or modification of your Personal Information;

  * the deletion of your Personal Data, including the deactivation of the service Job Alert.
